Thank you, Killua.
I owe it all to you.
It was like that ever since I woke up.
It was you, Killua.
If it means helping Gon,
I'm ready to do anything in my power.
But please don't forget,
out of all the people
Gon needs in his life,
he needs you the most.
[gasping]
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in English]
[singer singing in Japanese]
to ignore Meleoron's heartfelt protests
and appeared before them in the room
to force a confrontation with Pouf.
[Knuckle] Pouf.
[sighs]
The body that stands before you
is merely a shell.
My true core is on its way
to the King as we speak.
[sighs]
[gasps]
[intense music playing]
[narrator] Having recently
escaped from the cage of smoke,
Pouf confirmed that Knuckle and Morel
had indeed made contact
exactly as he suspected.
This was the right call.
The boss already told me
that you could make segments.
You're not lying.
[narrator] It was solely for Gon's benefit
Hang on.
Why are you telling me all this, anyway?
and had chosen not to share
this information with Pouf.
[Shaiapouf] Depending on his reason…
Answer me, damn it!
[Shaiapouf] My aim was to satisfy him.
[gasps]
and, for that, he needed
to leave the room peacefully.
I thought it might
put the boy's mind at ease.
He made it perfectly clear
that I was not to leave
this room for any reason.
I am only a segment
but what I seek is
a discussion and nothing more.
That is why I revealed the truth.
[narrator] Pouf knew
that when dealing with opponents
who would call him from behind
to challenge him,
appearing to tell the truth
would be far more effective
than relying on deception.
[Gon] You're lying.
[Shaiapouf gasps]
[Gon] Earlier…
you tried to sneak up
from behind and kill me.
You even admitted it.
Knuckle, don't let him fool you.
Is there any way that you can prove it?
[grunts]
[Knuckle] He's right.
[violin music playing]
Out of all of our enemies,
I dare say that he possesses
the strongest will of all.
But now, he's preoccupied with Pitou.
Perhaps I should be pleased by this.
It may yet work in our favor.
It's because of his iron will
and his incredible focus
that he's sitting there.
I would be putting myself
at a disadvantage,
so I can say nothing.
I'm afraid you will have to use
your own judgment.
Think it over.
Whether you come or not
is up to you!
[groans]
[Neferpitou] Please wait!
Look! I'm still right here!
I am so sorry about Pouf.
I'm the only one you need, right?
[Gon] Ten minutes.
[gasps]
You're just gonna have
to heal her ten minutes faster.
ignored Pouf's provocation
and slashed Pitou's deadline.
For how long?
How long should we wait?
and I can heal
her most critical injuries.
[narrator] Originally, Pitou had asked
for a greater amount of time
than was necessary.
This was to protect Komugi
and allow time for her
to heal completely.
Gon did not comply.
After a brief negotiation,
they agreed on one hour,
However, as a direct result
of experience,
Perhaps it was coincidence,
but it was likely that Gon
had only chosen ten minutes
to conform with Pouf's parting words.
Despite that probability,
because if I don't…
[roars]
I understand.
[Knuckle] Hmm.
[Gon] Knuckle…
I'll be fine here by myself.
his true core is headed for the King…
and the King is to the south.
[dramatic music playing]
[narrator] Gon and Killua
had seen everything
that had transpired up to this point,
but since Pitou
had no way of knowing this,
it was only natural to assume that Gon
had seen through Pouf's scheme
and already knew his plans.
[Neferpitou] I have to kill him,
no matter the cost.
I must, for the King's sake.
First, I must entrust her to someone else.
If I'm gone,
who will take Komugi to the King?
Gon, I can tell what you want to say,
believe me,
but it doesn't matter,
because I'm still gonna do things my way.
Youpi was…
[gasps]
No. No, never mind.
[narrator] Suddenly,
Knuckle realized that if what he said
made Gon hesitate even for a moment,
it could quite easily result in his death.
See ya.
[narrator] At the last second,
Knuckle managed to stop himself.
[Netero] Simple, really.
My subordinates were present
at your mother's deathbed.
She uttered your name
with her dying breath.
I bet I'm the only one who knows now.
Those same subordinates probably
died fighting your Royal Guard.
[wind blowing]
I'll make you a deal.
If you can force me to admit defeat,
I'll tell you your name.
[scoffs]
So I'll be playing
without a rook and bishop.
[Netero] When?
When did I start waiting
for my opponent
to make the first move?
[scoffs]
[yells]
Hah!
[thump]
[blow cracks]
[yells]
[man 1] Hah!
[thump]
[blow cracks]
[man 2] Yah!
When did I stop hesitating
and start graciously accepting
as they bowed their heads in defeat?
As if that was what I wanted!
That's not the height of perfection
that I sought for so long!
[boom]
I have always dreamt
of giving my heart and soul
to battle an unstoppable adversary.
[chorus vocalizing]
[Netero] This is a tomb.
Yours, as a matter of fact.
[chorus continues]
[rumbling]
[chorus ends]
Grateful for everything
that's led me to this point,
and to you.
[closing theme music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, "Zero and Rose."
[Killua] Yeah.
[Gon and Killua] The future is ours.
[singer singing in Japanese]